by H.
NOKIZAKA under construction
Boom! Here we go, NOKIZAKA Construction Work in progress!
I'm Bananaman, your host, and I look forward to working with you.
I'm Bananaman, your host.
Please come in.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well...
Ready?
Wow!
Oh, my God.
What a surprise!
Oh, I don't suppose you had it in your dressing room?
Yes, I did.
Sweets.
You didn't know? Catering.
Wasn't it in Mr. Himuro's dressing room?
What's going on?
Himuro-san really likes this kind of thing.
That's right. Himuro-san's like that.
He'd leave a gift like this and forget about it.
I'm usually very careful now.
I'm looking forward to going backstage later.
He really is like that.
So, today's project, Mr. Himuro, please.
The gimmick club.
It's actually a very important part of the variety show.
A gimmick who carries out missions behind the scenes.
This time, we'll be examining the gimmickry of the members on location.
It's not just for variety shows.
It's a job to be a gimmick.
If you can do this, you will get more work.
And those who are caught by the pure ones will also get more work.
This time, we will call the members to record a survey and interview for the show.
The gimmick person will set up various missions to the target.
The first challenge is a towel with four towels.The first challenge is a four-plane towel.
The first mission is to set up a buzzing cushion
Can you induce one of the four chairs to move and sit on one of the four chairs?
The trick of the challenger is a chiribiri pen
Can you make him use one of the three pens prepared?
And finally, the last challenge is to make the target drink the noodle soup that is hidden in the catering.
I have to say I'm going to drink this.
There are three of them.
I'm so nervous!
I was so nervous.
Are you sitting down?
Did you sit down?
It's easy for me to say, "I'm sitting down.
That doesn't happen very often.
But this should put him on his guard.
You're leading Persimmon to the buzzing cushion with a pretentious face.
That's good!
He easily passed the first mission with a smile and a laugh!
What a surprise!
I thought that's why there are four cushions...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll take that one.
Oh, you already have them?
You're dragging a booboo cushion.
You guys.
I'm scared of Kamry.
You're good.
That's good.
That's great.
I've already had the second one... and so have I.
It was chattering.
While the persimmon was fading on the booboo cushion.
While the persimmon was fading on the booboo cushion, Tamura was getting chiribiri chiribiri.
Tried the booboo cushion herself.Trying out the booboo cushion himself
to catch the persimmon even more off guard.
The result
It was a brilliant plan, and the mission was a success!
Was it true?
You're lying.
Push it.
What the hell?
It hurts.
Are you going for the second one?
Tamura proceeds so far without any suspicion
The last men-tsuyu mission!
How do you do this?
Can I drink it?
I think so.
I'll have a Coke.
Have a Coke.
That's a pickup artist's word.
Oh, yeah, that's good.
Here?
I haven't had a drink yet today.
That sounded like a Coke.
That's what it sounds like.
I don't know what's in there.
I wonder what this is.
Soy sauce?
I don't think so.
Japanese title.
Surika.
Oblivious to the oysters approaching from behind
The men-tsuyu is revealed
A painful mistake
You didn't.
Can you recover from this?Can we recover from this?
Certainly.
Drink this.
Dare I?
No, I can't.
No.
No, I'm just saying, maybe we're talking about the wrong thing.
Why not?
Well, we'll get him to drink it.
We'll make him drink it.
Oh, it's concentrated.
It's a super power play.
It's so obvious.
The cough, it's like he's telling his allies
It was really good
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it wasn't salty enough.
Just the right amount
He said it again.
After all that food, he ended the meal with a natural "boo-boo"!
Now you can't even tell he's a chef.
What do you think this place is?
What's this?
What do you think it is?
Play.
Tamura rolled the shaking persimmon in the palm of his hand
Mission accomplished!
The next trick was a tough one.
In addition to the booboo cushion and chattering pen
in addition to the booboo cushion chattering pen, he stuck a piece of nori (seaweed) from his lunch box on his teeth so that he wouldn't be recognized and startled.
The tooth remission challenge
It's hard to stick it on your teeth
The last one
It's hard!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Yay!
Yay.Yay!
Start choken
Tatzu, who took away the safe pen of Kazuwa in one room, succeeded
succeeded in getting the pen chattering in the blink of an eye!
Just take the back of the pen...
I'm chattering!
I don't have the power to set this up
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Let's open the door a little bit.
Good morning.
Oh, no, no, no!
What are you two doing?
It's gone. It fell.
Why did it fall?
Was it always there?
What's that? You know about this?
I didn't tell you.
The next pampering maneuver we tried to make him comfortable...
But it didn't work.
It happens, doesn't it?
I'm going to start writing an arcade for now.
Let's go again.
Did you have it made?
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
This is so hard to do, isn't it?
Shizuki doesn't even think about the error of his ways
Seimiya automatically sat back down
Wow!
Lucky Boo-Boo!
It's not Ray.
Oh, I see.
Cute.
Cute. This is cute.
No, it's cute.No, cute.
Cute.
Mr. Ray has won.
Tension Boom is already moving on to the third mission!
What?
The mission to move it.
Ah...
This is the hard part.
This is hard.
What? You didn't lift it.
Maybe you already have it.
I've got the groove.
I knew it!
I wish I could stay beside you all the time.
While Seimya is having a good time.
I'm secretly approaching Kanori.
You're early!
It's too soon!
The most important thing
This is the only thing
I'm keeping it for Jason.
LOL!
Cute.
Where the canoli is brilliantly set.
The opposition is unbeatable.
I didn't feel like I'm in nature itself.
So you're saying I can set it up?
Oh, no.
You mean I can set it up?
That's funny.
We had a few lucky breaks along the way.
But he completed the mission with overwhelming speed!
You're good, aren't you?Don't do it.
With Seymia.
I thought it was a little weird.
The chairs don't usually have mats like that.
on the top.
I thought it might have some kind of electric current running through it.
I sat down, scared, but there was nothing there.
When I pull it like this, it goes "Boo".
I see.
The next trickster is Kaki. He's going on a three-way mission against Kanagawa.
Kaki, both of them.
Kaki, after this?
After it's done.
Okay, let's try this again.
Sit here.
I'll sit there.
Takumi?
Takumi.
I failed to get him to sit on the booboo cushion.
And I couldn't get him to sit on the booboo cushion. And I couldn't get him to sit on the pen either.
While I was distracted by the lunch box, Kanagawa took the ordinary pen too!
Is this going to be the first time I've failed in all of my attempts?
What is this?
Let's have some tea!
What?
What's this about judging?
One taste.
Is this seaweed?
You're early.
That was quick.
Please add a word to Anpanman and make it a nightmare.
How many?
Poison Bus Anpanman.
LOL!
LOL!LOL!
That's great.
LOL!
I didn't do it on purpose.
You didn't know.
I knew it! It's because of the seaweed.
You're a genius.
Can I see it?
That seaweed is delicious!
As the leafy seaweed flowed, Kanagawa got up from his seat and went to the catering zone.
Here's where the persimmons move even more.
Can I see your face?
Yes, you can.
This is good.
Is it good?
What shall we do?
I want to make Anpanman look bad.
Poison gas anpanman.
Eww...
LOL!
Wait, wait, wait.
Wow!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What the hell are you doing with your hands?
Time's up for the two of you here.
I guess I can't do the Bilibili Pen.
But you made up for your mistake in the first half
Two missions completed.
It's good that they didn't give up.
Next, Tamura, Kaga, and Kanagawa tried the 3-man challenge!
Three people for a trick?
That's scary!I'm scared.
Endo is getting beat up by a bunch of guys.
The three of them are on a face exposure mission.
Kanagawa stands by with a cardboard box over his head.
to scare the target by approaching without being noticed.
In addition, a mission to dangle a member of the team set up outside the door
the first target out of the room.
I see.
It's not hard at all.
I'm sitting in front of the soccer.
I'll be sitting right in front of the football
I'll sit right in front of the soccer
At the beginning of the game, Kaki's shoulder tackle leads Endo to the target seat.
I'll make him sit in the best position for cardboard Kanagawa
I won't lie.
I've calmed down too.
Lying in life is the best thing you can do.
It's the best, isn't it?
I see. I'll come closer.
Can I have some tea?
Oh, no.
Make me look bad.
You can be the bad guy, Anpanman.
Like Anpanman, how much knowledge do you have?
I know a lot.
Yes, you do. You like Kaki, don't you?
Tabla leads the chion and attracts endo
finishing the cardboard and mentsue at the same time.
Here, the cardboard kanaga arrives right behind Endo
I can do it from the ignition.
You can't do it right behind
When you cut too much hair right in front of you
Aahh
I'm surprised at the cab candy.
Rebecca
I didn't find any.It wasn't there.
What's going on?
You're gonna be all right.
What do you think?
It's like... it's like... it's like Hokkaido... it's like Lime... it's like an undercover operation...
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Why?
With obviously dubious and mysterious excuses, Kanagawa joined us and started preparing for the next mission.
No, I want to go in the cardboard box too.
Don't go in there.
Let's go in, Sacchan!
I can't.
Come on, let's go in, Sachan.
Come on, let's go in.
Wait a minute, let me try too!
But you know, Kakki and Wan are pretty tall, right?
I'd like to switch places with you, too, Sachan.
I'd like to swap eyes.
Try it.
I doubt it. I doubt it.
How'd that work out for you?
Try it.
I didn't see it just now.
Did you see it? Did you see it?
He just forced the end to stand up and replaced the drink with something else.
Mediastinum.
Chumicho?
That's cute.
Then I want to put a top on it.Then I'd like to put a top on it.
What are you doing?
Switching it here. That's what I switched it with.
Oh, that's cute.
Oh, it's so cute!
What are you doing? Are you kidding me, you've got a questionnaire to fill out?
You're so cute!
So cute!
He's going to do it.
You haven't written a single one!
I'll write one.
Then how about a lie?
I once said I was late for a train, but I got off.
I did.
That's a big one.
You've got a big mouth.
Poor little Saku.
Poor little guy.
I won't drink it.
Ouch!
Is it good?
Tasty? Oh, my God.
What is it? It's thick.
Dark? It's strong.
Why? That's not a very strong reaction.
Why that reaction?
So, the last mission of the troupe
Can you lead us to the last mission of the troupe?
They won't call me.
Go get her.
How did you do that?
It's dense.
That's great.
You know, I don't...
I don't mind. You said you'd call it off.I don't mind. You said you'd call him out.
Say it once.
You like me, right?
And when you force Endo to come to the door...
You're scaring me.
You like me, don't you, Sakura?
No, you like me, don't you?
Cherry blossoms
Isn't there something wrong with you?
There's something different about this one.
Because...
You two are amazing.
It's the same as usual.
As usual, but...
As usual...
They drag the frightened Endo around from beginning to end.
All mission accomplished!
From here, let's take a look at Tsutsui's miscellaneous tricks.
First of all, in the balloon mission against Rika Sato
She cheated the sound with just her seat, and when she got the "luck line"...
Yay!
But when it comes to the movie version...
Wow!
That's right!
Surprise!
And the end doesn't bifork too?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What the hell? Why is it so scary?
And then there was the cardboard mission against Matsuno...
I approached him without any hesitation, standing on my knees, not caring about the noise...
Miyuki, you're going to notice, right?Miyuki, I think you're going to notice.
Wow!
Surprise, that one.
I don't think anyone is here.
They don't even notice this.
Just Rankin, who draws out Matsuno's reaction at the end of the messy trick...
What was it about the end that made everyone want to come closer together?
That's right!
The moment I came in, we all had so much momentum.
They were a bit of a bad bunch, weren't they?
I thought something might be wrong.
After that, the third term trickster, who's this?
Next, the third term student, Tokai, who went to Shikaku, tried two missions against Mezawa.
Please do me a favor.
I really want to take the time to fill out the questionnaire.
Are there so many different kinds of pens?
This one looks easy to write with.
This one's too thin.
What's that?
Umezawa was very wary of the suspicious pens right from the start.
But at least Sato was not suspected and the mission continued.
And Sato was wondering how men-tsuyu works.
What did you do to it?
Why did you do that?
That's scary.
Scary.
Something else is about to happen, a double-bottle style piece.
I'm gonna spill my weapon.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Spill it, spill it, spill it.
What are you doing?
Oh, my God.
I'm not good at this.
Oh, no, no, no, no!Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You always have them open the door for me, don't you?
I've never had it opened before.
Are you okay?
I flew so high.
This is great.
Is this the team you want to be on?
That's funny.
You know, you're the kind of creature that can't be bothered to drive a carpera.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, my God.
I'm good at this. I'm so good at this.
Hey, you're with me.
Because we have the same camera.
How did you not see that?
The lights came on.
The light hit me in the eye on the way out.
The electric light hit me in the eye on the way out.
I don't know which one is which.
It's normal.
Hmm?
There's something over there.
While the ever-vigilant Umezawa was wandering around the room...
Miraculously, he succeeded in swapping the pens.
And with this face.
But time ran out.
What do you think this is a location shoot for?
What?
Like a hidden camera in a kakka kuei.
I see.
I see... now.
Now?
No, I just thought something was weird.
First of all, there were three kinds of pens, right?
Where did I put the pen?Where did I put my pen?
What did you just do with it?
I don't know where my pen went.
I got it.
Ha-ha-ha.
Hey...
Always.
Oh, my God, aren't you good?
No, I'm not good.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm familiar with your reasoning.
I cracked my knuckles and completed mission 4.
Amazing!
Next, the three of us will aim to succeed in the three missions here in cooperative play!
Cardboard Umezawa and Sato standby in the room in advance.
Iwamoto enters the room with the target, Sakaguchi.
Iwamoto takes an ordinary pen and grabs Sakaguchi's pen, and the two of them start playing together.
Put this on.
Why did it ring?
Why didn't you put it on?
You're really good!
You're doing great!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
The three of us were having a great time.
Umezawa, the tall one, is gradually closing the distance
Ikekeke!
One more time!
Wow!
ohhhhhh!
oh oh oh!
Wow!
The advancing Umezawa approached Sakaguchi without being noticed at all by the team play of his peers.
His timing was perfect, too.
He showed a brilliant threat that blew away Sakaguchi beautifully!
Wow!Oh my god!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I don't know why I cried.
I just cried.
You shouldn't have made me sit there.
You scared me.
Oh, my God.
How far did you get?
It's been fun.
Let's fill out the questionnaire.
Scary!
And then, without any explanation, Umezawa made his next move.
He'll make the next move.
Thank you, Mr. Umezawa.
That sounds great.
There's a sound.
It's delicious. It's so good.
It's delicious.
It's not good.
Delicious?
So, all the missions are completed.
What do you think this is?
It's a weird room.
The set-up was smooth.
Sakaguchi was a little crazy.
You'd better take him by surprise.
Be careful. It's not always a surprise.
I heard that Izukawa-san and others were scared of him.
I thought it was another surprise, but it turned out to be true.
Scary, scary, scary!
Shiori Kubo's first photo book will be released on July 11
Mobile phone applications for the third round of the Tokyo leg of the national tour are now being accepted!
Next time, we will encounter an unexpected trick in the studio!